cabalonline.com 2007-12-10

# CABAL Online - The Revolution Of Action

**Privacy Policy**

Games.Masters.Com Limited is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. This privacy policy explains how we use the information we collect about you, how you can instruct us if you prefer to limit the use of that information and procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy. 

**1 The information we collect and how we use it**

When you register for our service we need to know your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number and expiry date and various other information . We gather this information to allow us to process your registration, process any orders you may make, market research, inform you of promotional things and assess what things may interest you. The relevant information is then used by us, our agents and sub-contractors to provide services to you,invoice you and to communicate with you on any matter relating to the conduct of your account and any offers relating to game and services offerded by games-masters.com ltd. We may also use aggregate information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring website usage in order to help us develop the website and our services and may provide such aggregate information to third parties. These statistics will not include information that can be used to identify any individual. 

We will also from time to time inform you of special events on games and new games we provide. We and/or our associated companies may also wish to provide you with information about special features of our website or any other games/services or products we think may be of interest to you. If you would rather not receive this information, please send a blank e-mail message to privacy1@games-masters.com. 

We and/or our associated companies may also wish to provide you with information about special features of our website or any other service or products we think may be of interest to you. ?If you would rather not receive this information, please send a blank e-mail message to webmaster@cabalonline.com. 

We may also want to provide you with related information from third parties we think may be of interest to you. From time to time we may provide your information to our customer service agencies for research and analysis purposes so that we can monitor and improve the services we provide. We or our agents and sub-contractors may contact you by post, e-mail or telephone to ask you for your feedback and comments on our services. If you would rather not receive this information, please send an e-mail to privacy2@games-masters.com. We may also provide your information to carefully selected third parties whose products or services we believe may be of interest to you. If you do not wish us to disclose your information in this way, please send an e-mail to privacy3@games-masters.com.

**2 How we protect your information**

The internet is not a secure medium. However we have put in place various security procedures as set out in this policy. Security measures such as firewalls are in place around the personal data processed. For example describe firewalls, browser certification technology, limited access, use of passwords etc as appropriate. We also keep your information confidential.

**3 Sale of business**

If this business is sold or integrated with another business your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and their advisers and will be passed on to the new owners of the business.

**4 Updating your details**

If any of the information that you have provided to Games.Masters.Com Limited changes, for example if you change your e-mail address, name or payment details or if you wish to cancel your registration, please let us know the correct details by sending an e-mail to privacyinfo@games-masters.com. 

**5 Your consent**

By submitting your information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. Continued use of the service will signify that you agree to any such changes. Owing to the global nature of the Internet infrastructure, the information you provide may be transferred in transit to countries outside the European Economic Area that do not have similar protections in place regarding your data and its use as set out in this policy. However, we have taken the steps outlined above to try to improve the security of your information. By submitting your information you consent to these transfers.

**6 How to contact Games.Masters.Com Limited**

We welcome your views about our website and our privacy policy. If you would like to contact us with any queries or comments please send an e-mail to privacypol@games-masters.com
